<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<News>
	<li>
		<assemblyVersion>1.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Hey! Now using news. Check out all the features in the settings window (maybe turn them on or off) or click the link.

Latest updates:
- Lots of overlays, and they auto-show when using certain tools.
- Caravans are auto-filled with things that are selected on the map.
- Blueprints can be designated with any stuff : right click the button to get the list
- Zone/Range highlighting looks a lot better (it's the corners)|img:AreaHighlightBad,AreaHighlightGood|

(Open mods settings to turn this on)
- Clicking names in Pawn tables (e.g. the Work tab) now highlight and select pawns just like clicking them on the map does, instead of closing the tab and jumping to them. Alt-click to close and jump like before.|img:TableSelection|</content>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1339135272</linkUrl>
	</li>
	
	<li>
		<assemblyVersion>1.1.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Geothermal vents are highlighted when building generators.
- Panning the camera with the middle-mouse button is better.
		</content>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1339135272</linkUrl>
	</li>

	<li>
		<assemblyVersion>1.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- ZOOM TO MOUSE. Turn it on in the settings.
(Also some old updates not yet mentioned:)
- Alert for workbench with no bills set up (now ignoring modded benches that don't use bills)
- An icon on the research tab showing if research is in progress
- Placing moisture pumps shows an overlay of current pump coverage
- Area manager can clear an entire area
- Clicking on the area jumps to adding to that area
- Dodge grenades can be ignored if a shield belt is worn
		</content>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1339135272</linkUrl>
	</li>

	<li>
		<assemblyVersion>1.2.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Paste Home/Roof area into other areas by right-clicking the paste icon|img:PasteHomeArea|
- Alerts for concerning levels of toxic buildup and heatstroke affecting your colonists (hypothermia already has an alert)
- Selected items for caravans and transport pods are saved when you close and re-open the same window
		</content>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1339135272</linkUrl>
	</li>

	<li>
		<assemblyVersion>1.2.4</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- New "Coverage" Overlay for selected buildings like trade beacons and moisture pumps, showing total coverage of all buildings
- Alert for wind-blocked turbines
- Resource readout is saved with your game, so loading your game will remember which categories to open
- Options in settings to hide the bottom-right toggle buttons
		</content>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1339135272</linkUrl>
	</li>

	<li>
		<assemblyVersion>1.2.5</assemblyVersion>
		<content>News in order of excitement (You'll need to turn some of these on)

- Color variation! A few fixes, and new features. Applies to apparel.
-- Fixes coloring of things made from steel ending up while (flak vests)
-- Ability to create things with pre-set colors varieties, like you see with raider armor
-- A universal, slight color variation, so every devilstrand shirt you make isn't the exact same color.
- With Zoom-To-Mouse, shift-zoom zooms to center
- Trade requests take your least valuable items first (still requiring normal quality)
- Trade windows can sort by "Value per kg"
- Transport pods re-build after launch
- Pawn tables (like Work/Wildlife) show an arrow pointing to hovered names
- A button to copy a policy (instead of just making a new, blank one)
- Low Food/Medicine alerts name the map they apply to, if you have multiple bases
- Show IED trap radius, even when placing other traps
		</content>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1339135272</linkUrl>
	</li>

	<li>
		<assemblyVersion>1.2.6</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- The bill option 'Count Equipped' can be enabled for any bill: to count medicine in inventories aswell
- Pawn table selection is re-vamped. Drag-select, Double-click to select all, Right-click to zoom without select.
		</content>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1339135272</linkUrl>
	</li>

	<li>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Areas are now tagged as 'for animals' or 'for colonists', and only show up for them if tagged. (Colony Manager should also respect this setting)
- An overlay toggle to show the power net
		</content>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1339135272</linkUrl>
	</li>

	<li>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.3</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- For selected items, there's a new button in the info panel to jump to them
- The forced slow-down after a battle can be cleared by shift-clicking the speed control
		</content>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1339135272</linkUrl>
	</li>

	<li>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.4</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Unlimited number of areas, scroll view in the area manager
		</content>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1339135272</linkUrl>
	</li>
</News>